Well, so, I would like to.
I bet you would like to, but that doesn't mean you're going to.
Are you?
No, no, no.
What I'm saying to you is the Congress has statutes on seditious conspiracy, on insurrection,
on impeding federal law enforcement.
The domestic terrorism statute in Congress obviously needs to be strengthened for domestic
terrorism in Congress.
We have foreign terrorism charges.
We have an entire patchwork of federal laws.
To the extent that there are charges that apply, we will charge them in every single
case.
You have impeding law enforcement.
You have seditious conspiracy.
You have a conspiracy to the private rights.
You have assault against law enforcement officers.
But all of this meets the hallmark textbook definitions of domestic terrorism.
I just want, Boris, I just want you, just for a moment, to step back and think about
what we're talking about here.
President Trump ran and won a campaign on turning back the border invasion.
You said that several times, Stephen.
You have the mayor of Chicago declaring a-
We have a limited amount of time, so let me ask you-
And I'll keep saying it.
Let me ask you about the governor of Illinois.
And he declared a no-go zone.
He declared a no-go zone for ICE.
We are set to hear from him in just moments.
How is that not insurrection?
Stephen, Stephen.
We're set to hear from J.B. Pritzker in just moments.
He says that you're attempting to inflame tensions and create a war zone.
He also says that you are profiling, that you're targeting black and brown people, even
those who turn out to be here legally.